Guide to the North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
- Organizational Documents, 1936-1999; 4 linear feet
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Marketing Association
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hog Marketing Program, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hog Marketing Program (Undated) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Milk/Dairy Marketing Program, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Milk/Dairy Marketing Program, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Milk/Dairy Marketing Program (Undated) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Broiler Marketing Program, 1970 - 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Broiler Marketing Program, 1972 - 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Fowl/Hen Marketing Program (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Apple Marketing Program (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Cucumber Marketing Program (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Vegetable Marketing Program (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Women's Committee
    - Constitution and Bylaws (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1947 - 1954 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1955 - 1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1958 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1961 - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1964 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1970 - 1971 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1974 - 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1976 - 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1978 - 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1981 - 1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1984 - 1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Awards and Accomplishments (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Women's Committee Minutes, 2008-2010 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1935-1984, undated
    - History and Philosophy, 1962-1963, 1984, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Association and By-Laws, 1935, 1949 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Documents
    - Information Day, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Scholarships (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Service Awards (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Historical Narratives (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Organizational Documents (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - The Services of Farm Bureau Signs Folder (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Farm Bureau Buildings (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Organizational History, Newspaper Clippings (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Agricultural Leaders, awards, pamphlets, and ephemera (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Board Meeting, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Districts and Field Representative Maps (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Employee Directory (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - County Presidents, Liaisons, etc. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Officers and Directors, 1978-2010 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Insurance on Board Members (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Ag in the Classroom Website Materials (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Paul Shackelford papers, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Paul Shackelford papers, 1970-1971 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Paul Shackelford papers, 1973-1994 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Reference Publications: American Farm Bureau Federation Reference Publications (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Reference Publications: Miscellaneous (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Reference Publications: North Carolina Department of Agriculture (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Reference Publications: North Carolina State Historic Sites (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Reference Publications: United States Department of Health and Human Services (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - NCFB Annual Reports, 2010 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Rules of Order and Parliamentary Procedure for Farm Bureau, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Policies, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Policies, 1982-1983 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Policies, 1984-1985 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Policies, 1986-1987 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Policies, 1988-1989 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Policies, 1990-1991 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Policies, 1992-1993 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Policies, 1994-1995 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Policies, 1998-1999 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Policy Resolution for 2003 (1 of 3) (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Policy Resolution for 2003 (2 of 3) (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Policy Resolution for 2003 (3 of 3) (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations of the Resolutons Committee to the Voting Delegate (Part 1), 2002 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations of the Resolutons Committee to the Voting Delegate (Part 2), 2002 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations of the Resolutons Committee to the Voting Delegate (Part 3), 2002 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Policies, 2003-2004 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Policies, 2005-2006 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Policy Review Day, 2007 Policies (1 of 2) (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Policy Review Day, 2007 Policies (2 of 2) (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Policies, 2008-2009 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Policies, 2009-2010 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000s (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten, 2005 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten, 2001 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten(1 of 3), 2002 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (1 of 4), 2003 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (2 of 4), 2003 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (3 of 4), 2003 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence of Larry Wooten (4 of 4), 2003 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Member Biographies (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - NCFB Accent on Agriculture Index, 1981-1982 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - NCFB, Leader-Gram, January 2006-April 2010 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - NCFB News Releases, 1995-2003 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - NCFB Records of Photocopies and Meter Readings, 1999-2003 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - NCFB Accent on Agriculture (1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - NCFB Accent on Agriculture (2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - NCFB Farm Bureau News, Rate Cards for Advertisement, 2000-2006 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - NCFB Correspondence Lists, , May 2001 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Inventory Records, Misc. Camera Equipment and Other, 1980s-1990s (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - TV Vehicle Records (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Young Farmer and Rancher Program and Accent on Agriculture (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - NCFB Identity theft coverage, announcement of Wooten's presidency, safemark tire and battery pamphlet (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - NCFB insurance Company information (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - NCFB Legal Foundation (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Public Relations and Publicity Ephemera (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - NCFBscript, 1936-1985 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - NCFB 77th Annual Convention Procedures (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - NCFB Farm Bureau Magazine and LeaderNCFB, Farm Bureau News, assorted issues, 1985-2013 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - NCFB News, February 1952-May 1955 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - NCFB Farm Bureau News, January 1947-January 1952 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Special Programs, Happenings Newsletter, , Spring 1980 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Special Programs, Planning Guides, 1990-1992 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Special Programs, Planning Guides, 1992-1995 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - NCFB Media Workshop Binder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - NCFB Media Workshop Information (1 of 2) (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - NCFB Media Workshop Information (2 of 2) (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - NCFB New Employee Orientation, Jul-85 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - NCFB Political Action Committee (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Marketing Materials: NCFB Dairy Report, Commodity Digest, Hog Marketing Report and related materials (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - NCFB Hog Marketing Program Materials (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - NCFB E-Team Nomination Form, 2013-2014 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - AFBF and NCFB Policy, 2012 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - NCFB 76th Annual Meeting Materials (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Printed Materials, 1948-1998; 3 linear feet
  The series of Printed Materials is divided into subseries that represent the major divisions of the North Carolina Farm Bureau. For the North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, the primary document circulated through the organization was its annual policies. Arranged chronologically, these policies document the resolutions adopted by the Farm Bureau at its annual meetings. Often times, these policies also reflect and approve national resolutions proposed by the American Farm Bureau Federation. The Federation subseries also includes miscellaneous propaganda pamphlets circulated by the organization. The next subseries lists the General Manager's Reports for the North Carolina Farm Bureau Mutual Insurance Company. Although the chronological list reveals several lapses, this subseries does contain all reports accessioned with the collection. Third, the printed materials circulated by the North Carolina Farm Bureau Service Company are dominated by price lists for Safemark products offered by the program. Finally, the subseries for the North Carolina Farm Bureau Women's Committee contains handbooks that reveal the goals and objectives of the group.
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation
    - Policies
      - 1948 - 1951 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - 1952 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 1956 - 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - 1960 - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - 1963 - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 1966 - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 1968 - 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - 1970 - 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - 1972 - 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - 1974 - 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 1976 - 1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 1978 - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - 1980 - 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - 1982 - 1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - 1986 - 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - 1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Other Publications
      - Farm Bureau News (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Farm Bureau News, 1980s (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Farm Bureau News, 1990s (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Farm Bureau News, , early 2000s (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Farm Bureau News, 2010s (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Farm Bureau News, North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation Magazine (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Accent on Agriculture, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Accent on Agriculture, January, 1994 - April, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Accent on Agriculture, May, 1994 - December, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Accent on Agriculture, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Accent on Agriculture, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Accent on Agriculture, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Accent on Agriculture (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Pamphlets, 1940s (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Pamphlets, 1950s (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Pamphlets, 1960s (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Miscellaneous Pamphlets, including drawing of Raleigh building, program of Mangum, and autographed pamphlet from Democratic candidate Frank Bryant (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Ordinary Women, Extraordinary Service (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - NCFB, Other Publications, Continuous Coverage, 1980s (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Cotton Newsletters and Reference Materials, 1980s-1990s
      - Cotton Classing, 1993 - 1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Cotton Classing, 1995 - 1997 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Cotton Economic Review, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Cotton Economic Review, March - August 1993 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Cotton Economic Review, September - December 1993 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Cotton Economic Review, March - June 1994 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Cotton Economic Review, July - December 1994 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Cotton Economic Review, 1995 - 1996 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Cotton Leader, 1990 - 1994 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Cotton Leader, 1995 - 1998 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Cotton Marketing News, December 1995 - June 1996 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Cotton Marketing News, July 1996 - April 1997 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Cotton Marketing News, May 1997 - October 1997 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Cotton Marketing News, November 1997 - April 1998 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Cotton Marketing News, May 1998 - December 1998 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Cotton Marketing Weekly, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Cotton Marketing Weekly, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Cotton Marketing Weekly, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Cotton Marketing Weekly, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Cotton Marketing Weekly, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Cotton Physiology Today, 1993 - 1995 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Cotton Physiology Today, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Cotton's Week, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Cotton's Week, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Cotton's Week, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Cotton's Week, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Cotton's Week, January - June 1997 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Cotton's Week, July - December 1997 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Cotton's Week, January - June 1998 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Cotton's Week, July - December 1998 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Cotton Incorporated, 1993 - 1998 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Cotton Economic Review, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Cotton Economic Review, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Gin Press, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Gin Press, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Cotton Referenee Material, 1990s (Carton 91)
      - Cotton Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 93)
      - Cotton Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 94)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Mutual Insurance Company
    - General Manager's Reports
      - 1969 - 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - 1972 - 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - 1974 and 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - 1978 - 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - 1980 - 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - 1985 - 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - 1987 - 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - 1989 - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Service Company
    - Safemark Price Lists
      - 1967, 1970 - 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - 1974 - 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - 1976 - 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - 1979 - 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - 1983 and 1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - 1989 and 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Women's Committee
    - Handbooks
      - 1949, 1951 -1952 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - 1953 -1954 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - 1955 -1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - 1957 -1958 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - 1959 and 1961 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - General Publications
      - Program Listings (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Womens' committee programs and guides (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Womens' committee programming binder (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Womens' committee records (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Womens' program guidebooks (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Womens' program slideshow (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Food Check-Out Day folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Farm Womens' Forum Newsetter, 1986-1988 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1948-1989
    - Policies, 1953-1989
      - 1953-1963 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - 1964-1976 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - 1977-1985 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - 1986-1989 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Brochures, 1953-1958, undated
      - “This is Farm Bureau”, 1972, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1955, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Other State and Regional Farm Bureaus, 1953-1958
    - Southern Farm Bureau, Brochures, 1953, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Farm Bureau Women, Brochures, 1953-1958 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Other State and Regional Agricultural Organizations, 1951-1970, undated
    - Brochures, circa 1951, 1966-1970, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Annual Meetings and Conferences, 1938-1991; 1 linear feet
  This series focuses on the materials collected at and pertaining to the annual meetings and other miscellaneous conferences sponsored by the North Carolina Farm Bureau. Remarks by the President of both the North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation and the North Carolina Farm Bureau Mutual Insurance are included.
  - Annual Reports
    - 1947 - 1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 1951 and 1953 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 1987 - 1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 1989 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - President's Remarks
    - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation
      - 1975 - 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - 1979 - 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - 1983 - 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - 1987 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina Farm Bureau Mutual Insurance Company
      - 1976 - 1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - 1981 - 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - 1985 - 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - 1988 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Programs
    - 1947 - 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - 1951 - 1955 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - 1956 - 1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - 1961 - 1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 1966 - 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - 1971 - 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 1976 - 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 1981 - 1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - 1986 - 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - General Conference Documents
    - Annual Meeting Committee Assignments (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting Awards, 1985 - 1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting Awards, 1988 - 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1940s and 1950s (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1938-1989
    - Resolutions, 1940-1951 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1938, 1940-1946 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1952, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Programs, 1969, 1972, 1981-1989 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Dixie Special, 1952, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Text of Remarks by the President of the United States, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Women’s Committee, Candlelighting Service, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Other State and Regional Farm Bureaus, 1960
    - Annual Report, Michigan Farm Bureau, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Legal and Legislative Material, 1962-1999; 11 linear feet
  The largest series of the collection, this group of records elaborates upon the many legal, legislative, and financial undertakings of the North Carolina Farm Bureau. Topics include legislation of issues regarding cotton, dairy, livetsock, peanuts, and poultry. Tobacco legislation dominates the subseries of legal materials, indicating the emphasis and importance the Farm Bureau placed on this often controversial topic.
  - Legal Materials
    - General Legal and Legislative Information (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Lawsuits: Leaf Tobacco Exporters Case, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Lawsuits: Leaf Tobacco Exporters Case, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Lawsuits: Leaf Tobacco Exporters Case, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Lawsuits: Leaf Tobacco Exporters Case, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Lawsuits: Marshall v. Horne Walston (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lawsuits: Price v. Block (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Materials
    - Cotton Legislation
      - 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - 1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - 1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - 1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - 1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - 1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - 1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Dairy Legislation
      - 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - 1994 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - 1995 - 1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - 1997 - 1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Livestock Legislation
      - 1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - 1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - 1992 - 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - 1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - 1996 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - 1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - 1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - 1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - 1998 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Pseudorabies Information, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Peanut Legislation
      - 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - 1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - 1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - 1979 - 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - 1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - 1988 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - 1988 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - 1989 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - 1990- General Information (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1990- General Information (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - 1990- General Information (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - 1990- Legislative Amendments (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - 1990- News Articles (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - 1994- Statistics (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 4)